https://www.hawk-conservancy.org/about/privacy/

Red Kite ecology
How many Buzzards are there?
Where do Red Kites and Buzzards live, and why?
Red Kite ecology
How many Buzzards are there?
Where do Red Kites and Buzzards live, and why?
Privacy Statement for the Hawk Conservancy Trust
The Hawk Conservancy Trust has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our commitment to privacy online. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for this website.
Our site uses cookies to keep track of your shopping cart.
Customer contact information collected in the shop is used only to fulfill the order. If you email us, your email address will be retained in case we need to contact you again about your enquiry. We currently have no plans to conduct mass emailing. If we do, it will be stated here.
This site contains links to other sites. The Hawk Conservancy Trust is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such websites.
Our site uses order forms for customers to request information, products, and services. We collect visitor’s contact information (like their email address) and financial information (like their account or credit card numbers). Contact information from the order form is used to send orders to our customers. The customer’s contact information is used to get in touch with the visitor when necessary. If users opt in they may also receive marketing information but can opt out at any time. Financial information that is collected is used to bill the user for products and services.
We may occasionally run contests on our site in which we ask visitors for contact information (like their email address) and demographic information (like their postal code, age, or income level). The customer’s contact information is used to contact the visitor when necessary. When entering a competition users may opt in to receive future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below.
Security
This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. No personal information is retained on our web server. Order information is held on our web server only until it is successfully transmitted to our shop. During that time, financial information, like Credit Card numbers, is held in encrypted form and only rendered into plain text on arrival at our shop.
Opt In
If a user has opted in to receive marketing communications from us and our partners they may opt out at any time via the unsubscribe link contained in each email.
Users may request removal of their information from our database to not receive future communications or to no longer receive our service by sending an email to unsubscribe@hawkconservancy.org
If users would ever like us to remove them from our records and/or never contact them or change their details, or how they would like to be contacted, please call 01264 773850 or email dataprotection@hawkconservancy.org.
Corrections and Updates
Users may request changes and modification to information previously provided by sending an email to info@hawkconservancy.org. Users may also request a copy of any personal information we hold via the same address.
National Bird of Prey Hospital™ Contacts
If a member of the public brings a wild bird for treatment or rehabilitation to our National Bird of Prey Hospital™, we ask for their name, address and telephone number.  We will only use this contact data to inform them of progress of the bird or to ask further questions about how the bird was found, in order to administer appropriate treatment.
This data is stored in paper files and retained for three years and then destroyed.  We do not share this data with anyone else except to use on our behalf.
Contacting the website
If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this website, you can contact or any general questions about how data is stored and used, please contact:
The Hawk Conservancy Trust, Weyhill, Andover, Hampshire, SP11 8DY
info@hawkconservancy.org
01264 773850
A member of
A member of
Visit
Plan Your Visit
Daily Activities
Daily timetable
Red Kite ecology
How many Buzzards are there?
Where do Red Kites and Buzzards live, and why?
Overseas Projects
Pakistan Vulture Restoration Project
Ecology of the Hooded Vulture
Poison Response Action
On-site Projects
National Bird of Prey Hospital™
Publications
Internships
©2020 Hawk Conservancy Trust
We use cookies to ensure that we give you the best experience on our website. If you continue to use this site we will assume that you are happy with it.OkRead more
